http://www.kinglear.sitesuite.com.au/privacy-statement.html

Privacy Statement
SiteSuite’s website Privacy Statement has been included on line so as to provide you with a clear indication of how SiteSuite complies with privacy legislation.
Your privacy is important to SiteSuite.
If you visit an area of the SiteSuite website to which you are not required to log on in order to read, browse or download information, SiteSuite's systems may record the date and time of your visit, the pages visited and any information downloaded. SiteSuite's systems will not record any information that would identify you personally without your consent.
Information collected
When you look at this web site, SiteSuite Website Design Pty Ltd makes a record of your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:
your server address
your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc)
the pages you accessed and documents downloaded
the previous site you have visited
the type of browser you are using.
If you choose to provide us with your e-mail address, SiteSuite may notify you about changes to our web sites, and to inform you of services, opportunities and special events that SiteSuite believes that you'll find valuable.
From time to time we may also use the information to send you information about us, our related companies and possibly about third parties (we will send such information directly to you - your information will not be provided to third parties without your consent).
To facilitate our efficient use of your information, and to provide you with the best recruitment and contracting services and/or opportunities, it may sometimes be necessary for SiteSuite to disclose your information to third parties. However, this disclosure will only occur in the following circumstances:
To our Employees, Contractors and Agents
From time to time we may engage or employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Such parties will have access to only that personal information required by them to perform their functions, and may not use such information for any other purposes.
Where required by Law
In certain circumstances we may be required by law to disclose your personal information, for example, where disclosure is ordered by a Court, or subpoenaed in relation to third party litigation. We also reserve the right to choose to disclose your information to law enforcement agencies in circumstances described in the National Privacy Principles and other applicable laws and regulations, including for the purpose of investigating alleged contraventions of the law.
Cookies
Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. SiteSuite allocates a cookie to each Internet browser that visits its web site. This cookie does not allow SiteSuite to collect personally identifiable information about you. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our website. In addition, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser.
IP Address
SiteSuite's web servers gather your IP address to help diagnose problems with our service, to administer our site, and to gather broad demographic information. Demographic information is gathered in aggregate only and cannot be traced to an individual user.
Off Site Links
SiteSuite may provide links to other sites. SiteSuite is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these web sites. Your activity on those sites is covered by the privacy policies on those sites.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us, you can contact us at our Sydney Office:
SiteSuite Website Design Pty. Ltd. Level 3, 122 Walker Street North Sydney NSW 2060, Australia.
© Copyright SiteSuite Website Design (WebUX P/L). All rights reserved. Websites Made Easy. Privacy Statement Sitemap
TALK TO US
info@sitesuite.com.au
